http://www.martinsexton.com/privacy-policy

Join Mailing List
Privacy PolicyMartinSexton.com’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using MartinSexton.com, located at http://www.MartinSexton.com and its directly associated domains (collectively, “MartinSexton.com” or “Website”)By using or accessing MartinSexton.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.When you visit MartinSexton.com you provide us with personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.When you register with MartinSexton.com, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.When you use MartinSexton.com, you may set up your personal profile, We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer our features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, we can send you a package of materials when you sign up for a street team campaign. When you update information, we may keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.You post User Content (as defined in the MartinSexton.com Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on MartinSexton.com is a violation of the MartinSexton.com Terms of Service and should be reported through email at: info@MartinSexton.comBy using MartinSexton.com, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.
Martin Sexton's Mailing List Sign Up
*After submitting your email address for this list, you will receive an email to verify
your subscription. Click on the link in the email to verify to receive the Martin Sexton Newsletters.
